first let's talk about intentions
首先让我们谈谈意图
intentions can be activated by pressing
意图可以通过按下来激活
alt enter this will bring up a list of
alt输入此内容将弹出一个列表
actions that you can carry out inside
您可以在内部执行的操作
the editor there are two types of
编辑器有两种类型
intentions ones that try to anticipate
试图预见的意图
which are intended to write from a
旨在从
statement or expression that hasn't been
尚未出现的陈述或表达
parsed correctly or from a symbol it
正确解析或从符号解析
isn't recognized here this member
在此成员未被识别
variable is being accessed from a static
从静态访问变量
context and so I have two options here I
上下文，所以我在这里有两个选择
can choose to make the member variable
可以选择使成员变量
static or to make the surrounding
静态或使周围
context not static and so I'll choose to
上下文不是静态的，所以我选择
make that variable static and the arrow
使该变量静态和箭头
will go away for any error inside the
将消失的内部任何错误
editor we try to provide an Associated
编辑器我们尝试提供一个关联的
fix for it or a quick fix it's called
解决它或称为快速修复
and you can activate those whenever you
您可以随时激活它们
see the light bulb next to your cursor
看到光标旁边的灯泡
if you know so press alt enter to show
如果您知道，请按Alt输入
in your intention actions here and here
您在这里和这里的意图行动
for instance this method expects return
例如，此方法期望返回
type of boolean and so in order to
布尔类型，以便
correct this I can either make it return
纠正这个我可以让它返回
void or add a return statement I'll add
无效或添加返回语句
the return statement and that error will
返回语句，该错误将
go away and then finally I have some
走开，最后我有一些
duplicate methods down here and since
重复的方法在这里，因为
they share the same signature I'll need
它们共享我需要的相同签名
to delete one of them so I can do that
删除其中一个，这样我就可以做到
by navigating to the name of the method
通过导航到方法的名称
and safe deleting it finally if I remove
并安全删除它，如果我删除了
the import statement or this ArrayList
导入语句或此ArrayList
and this creates another error I can
这会造成另一个错误
quickly add that back in by just
只需将其快速添加回
pressing alt enter no recognizes this is
按alt输入否识别这是
inside Java util and it gives me the
Java util中，它给了我
import statement and so once we've
导入声明，所以一旦我们
eliminated all the errors inside our
消除了我们内部的所有错误
source code there's usually a few
源代码通常有一些
warnings that are left and these are
剩下的警告是
also available inside the gutter to your
也可在装订线内
right you'll be able to see all of those
好的，您将能够看到所有这些
regions inside your code they're
您代码中的区域
highlighted yellow you can also navigate
突出显示的黄色，您也可以浏览
to them by pressing
通过按给他们
- this will take you to the next warning
-这将带您进入下一个警告
or error inside your editor these are
或编辑器中的错误是
also regions that have triggered an
也触发了
intention and you can see inside the
意图，你可以看到里面
intention list I can choose to remove
我可以选择删除意向列表
this field since it isn't being read or
此字段，因为它未被读取或
I can create a getter and a setter to
我可以创建一个getter和setter
encapsulate it and so if I navigate to
封装它，所以如果我导航到
the next one then I can either safe
下一个我就可以安全了
delete this in math Lin since it's never
删除数学林中的它，因为它永远不会
been called inside the entire project or
在整个项目中被称为
I can choose to leave it if I'd like
如果愿意，我可以选择离开
these are warnings because they don't
这些是警告，因为它们不
necessarily have to be addressed but the
必须解决，但
IDE recognizes that there may be a
IDE认识到可能存在
problem or something that it can fix so
问题或可以解决的问题
it will alert you and give you quick fix
它会提醒您并快速修复
to address that problem
解决这个问题